好的，我们已经定义了一个模板
Okay, so we've defined a template for
列出一些事情并将它们组合起来。
taking a list of things and combining them.
我们将调用该函数折叠，实际上折叠地图。
We're going to call that function fold, actually fold map.
我们将把它映射成一个类型，然后通过 concat 将它折叠起来。
We're gonna take this, map it into a type and then fold it down via concat.
所以我不想在这里评价折叠地图。
So I don't wanna rate fold map here.
我只是要把它从图书馆带来。
I'm just gonna bring it in from a library.
所以我们称这个为const。
So we'll call this const.
我的意思是，我们基本上只是做了右折叠地图，
I mean, we essentially just did right fold map,
我们只需要传入这种类型和那种类型。
we'll just have to pass in this type and that type.
但我要继续说清单。
But I'm just gonna go ahead and say list.
我们将需要 immutable-ext。
We're gonna require immutable-ext.
不可变分机。
Immutable-ext.
凉爽的。
Cool.
这定义了列表中的完整地图，
And that defines full map on the list,
因为我们不能在数组上调用完整映射，对吗？
because we can't call full map on an array, right?
所以我只是使用列表来调用完整的地图。
So I'm just using the list to be able to call full map.
现在我不需要这些了。
And now I don't need any of this.
[笑] 我只想说把它全部放进去，完整地映射它。
[LAUGH] I'm just gonna say put it into all, full map it.
伟大的。
Great.
提供所有这些空的可能会有所帮助
And it's probably helpful to provide all that empty
因为那样我们就会有一个起始值。
because then we'll have a starting value.
我们将其称为 toJS，因为它是不可变的。
And we'll call it toJS because it's immutable.
美好时光。
Good times.
并运行这个。
And run this.
再一次，它不是找到不可变的，toJS 不是一个函数。
Again, it's not findking immutable, toJS is not a function.
因为它正在将它从列表中折叠出来。
Because it's folding it out of the list.
这有点意思。
That's kind of interesting.
它正在消耗它，对吧？
It's consuming it, right?
它把它变成了一个全部，所以我们把列表减少到一个全部
It's turning it into an all, so we reduced the list into an all so
我们实际上不必调用 toJS。
we don't actually have to call toJS.
凉爽的。
Cool.
仍然有效。
Still works.